When we did our bachelor's work, we worked in a team of eight people throughout the semester.
They have taken 3D scans, inside the actual mines, up in Kiruna.
As they read to data file.
And we developed an algorithm that can,
Our node graph generates itself.
Then they can do simulations
that makes you can see where it becomes most worthwhile
to break ore, and that can do it for any mine.
It got very cool because it is actually used by LKAB's system today.
I think anyone can search!
It is a bit sad that there is a stereotype today, which you see a lot in movies and TV series.
That people who program are super -smart, self -taught and sit completely alone in any basement
and hack into institutions while